This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Bucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew, Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, Impel Down.
Together with Captain Buggy, as well as former Baroque Works agents, Mr. Three and Bonclay,
Luffy was able to make his way to level four, the Burning Heat Helm.
But as soon as he arrived, he was poisoned by Magellan, the Warden of Impel Down,
and taken into custody.
After Luffy was imprisoned on level five, the Freezing Hell,
Bonclay did everything in his power to find a way to save him.
No freaking way!
I mean, uh, what do you mean you can't make an antidote?
What's the hold-up?
A miracle?
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
I forgot about him!
He's in Impel Down!
My hero!
The miracle worker!
Come on!
We need to find out where they're holding him now!
A paradise in hell!
Impel Down level 5.5!
Uh-oh.
I think we're surrounded.
Well then, we have no choice.
We should lock ourselves inside.
Right, I'll try to distract the mutts.
Make it quick!
Chew or miss!
My special muggy ball!
Good riddance!
What the hell?!
Now I've done it!
Yeah, you did?
Yep, I broke the key!
Why are you so useless?
Crap, it's too late!
Take this!
Candles!
No!
That was close.
Come on, move!
Let's make a run for the cell pronto!
I don't think that we'll need to.
I just had an idea.
Stupid wolf!
Try and eat us now, you frozen fleabags!
It's no use trying to bite your way through, Mr. Wolf.
This candle house is as hard as iron.
Even with fangs so big and powerful as yours,
there's no way you'll break it!
You said it!
Let's head out!
But of course, my friend!
One, two!
Maybe you're not useless!
I'm so happy right now, I'll take that as a compliment!
One, two!
After a while, it gets kind of heavy.
That makes sense.
I made it thicker than usual to protect us.
Oh, yeah?
Well, good thinking.
How fast we move doesn't really matter.
As long as we're safe,
all we gotta do is make it to the stairs
and we can get out of this hellhole.
Indeed.
And while we remain inside this cell,
we keep out of the wind, too.
It's a win-win.
Let's move!
One, two, one!
Wait!
Take a few steps back, would you?
Huh?
Something up?
Something is odd.
Look, outside.
What happened to all of those wolves?
You're right.
They're gone.
You don't suppose they gave up?
Do you hear something?
Huh?
Uh-oh.
It's winter wolf sting underground!
Who the hell is that?
He's covered in blood.
Before...
I...
I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen!
Running is the only answer!
I'm sorry, Strawboy.
I'm a coward.
Forgive me!
I ran away.
Hey, pal.
How do you...
know him?
He's my friend!
Strawboy!
I'm not letting you die!
Come on!
We better go!
He left the keys?
I never thought about breaking out of here until now.
I gotta find Eva before it's too late!
Eva, huh?
I have no idea where that Twinkle Toes went.
Who the hell wants to know, anyway?
Emporio Ivankov.
Oh, that guy.
Yeah.
He's probably dead.
Who are you staring at?
That guy's been missing for ages.
What do you even want with him?
And how did you get out of your cell?
Get me out of mine, too!
Do you know why they're keeping a man named Eva?
Hey, you!
What's wrong?
Hey!
Speak up!
Answer me!
Don't bother!
Didn't you notice?
Everyone in that cell is frozen stiff!
How about you, then?
Yeah.
I heard ya.
Said you're looking for Ivankov.
Right?
Yeah.
Do you know something?
Look.
Over there.
You see that forest?
Yes.
There's an abandoned jailhouse.
Way beyond the tree line.
A while back,
I saw this strange guy
just dancing around out there.
Really?
Yeah, I think it was him.
It's worth a look.
Thanks, friend.
We're all in this together.
That forest.
It's where the wolves live.
Oh, is it?
Every so often, people disappear in Impel Town.
We're sure they didn't just break out,
as some of the missing could barely move.
They just vanished without a trace,
and no one seems to know the cause.
We've come to call it demon-ing away.
All the guards here have come to fear
these unnatural and strange disappearances.
We believe that those missing
have been dragged to the gates of hell.
Hence why we call it what we do.
The gates of hell?
Demon-ing away?
Quit pulling my tail.
No way Eva disappeared
because of some superstitious mumbo-jumbo.
I've never met him myself,
but his reputation certainly precedes him.
Even in a hell like this place,
I'm sure he can still make a miracle happen.
Because Eva is our queen, our god!
Somehow, I know he can save Straw Boy.
If we can't count on an antidote anymore,
he's his only chance.
Eva, I swear I'll find you no matter what.
No!
Ahhhh!
Straw Boy!
What do you think you're doing to my friend Bon?
Leave him?
No!
Oh, Straw Boy! How... did you...
The Public Execution of Five Fist Ace will take place in 26 hours.
The Public Execution of Five Fist Ace
Damn it all. Where did you go?
This place is, like, stupid hot. It's so... steamy.
Young, gorgeous, just my type! Woohoo! She's hot enough to light hell on fire!
Wait a minute. Priorities. Where's the pansy prisoner who beat up all the guards? He's gotta be around here somewhere.
Wait, who are you? Who are you?
Who I am? Doesn't really matter right now, lover boy. Can I get some assistance here?
Huh?
Can't you see how sweaty I am? Oh, surely you can help me out of these racks. Please?
We can do it in here, right?
Yep. One sec.
One sec.
Okay, chink. Ladies first.
Oh, no!
We can do it in here, right?
Yep. One sec.
Can I have a chink? Ladies first.
Oh, my. It's dark in here. No need to be shy.
Why did you do it in here?
Oh, my boy. Can I get some assistance here?
Can I get some assistance here?
Huh?
Can't you see how sweaty I am?
Oh, surely you can help me out of these racks. Please?
Oh, no!
We can do it in here, right?
Yep. One sec.
Can I have a chink?
Ladies first.
Oh, my. It's dark in here. No need to be shy.
Where did you run off to?
I'm right here.
This is the worst day ever.
I'll just blame it on the warden, of course.
I can't believe that a prisoner outsmarted me.
When do I get to be the warden?
Oh, I used too much poison. Oh, my tummy.
That's right. We got the riot shut down.
All of the prisoners have been returned to their cells
and we've retrieved the keys, but...
I think some are missing.
Damn it. What a pain.
Listen up. You've got to find him.
He must be somewhere on this floor.
Find him and I'm going to whip the sass right out of him.
Yes, mistress.
Several hours later, Von Clay starts to wake up.
Where am I?
Strawboy!
Ah!
Where did he go?
Strawboy!
I think I hear people talking somewhere.
This is it!
Ah!
So bright!
Well, you decided to join us, did ya?
You were sleeping forever. Want a drink?
Ah!
Praise him for the newcomer, everyone!
Cheers!
We've been watching you guys.
On our monitors.
Bravo! Quite the show!
What?
I'll seat you.
What floor did you come from, by the way?
We've got plenty to eat here.
I'd guess you're hungry.
Wait!
Where am I?
Where's Strawboy?
What?
Do you think you somehow magically made it out of the prison?
Don't worry.
You're still an impel down, sweetie.
No way!
That's a lie!
No one's wearing any prison clothes!
Everyone's drinking and having fun!
Did I wake up in some kind of paradise?
What's the deal?
Hold on.
I remember.
I was chased down and attacked by those wolves.
Then Strawboy woke up and helped me.
After that, I passed out.
Then maybe I am dreaming.
Oh, wait!
What if I died from the cold and I'm in heaven now?
Close, but no cigar.
Huh?
You've been sleeping like a baby.
Out cold for ten hours now.
Ten hours?
Are you kidding me?
And who are you?
My name is Inazuma.
Hmm.
Mind your manners.
I'm the one who fetched you from that bitter cold, after all.
You're lucky you two didn't die from exposure.
Wait!
Did you say you two?
So you brought Strawboy here too?
Well then, where is he?
Speak up!
Answer me!
Damn you!
There's no time!
Patience now.
Let him explain things to you.
Him?
Who?
Oh, the lights are down!
It's time!
The show's starting!
You'll want a front row seat.
What is this?
Did you sleep tight, little candy boy?
Or should I say, little bum boy?
How do you know my name?
Oh, thank you for coming.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Shaker!
Dixie!
To get here, you have to pass through the sewers of Impel Down.
Following paths that shouldn't exist to a place beyond imagination.
It's a prisoner's paradise.
We've got every pleasure you could ever beg for right here.
Drinks.
Weapons.
Games.
But most of all, we have freedom!
Yeah!
You said it!
We got our freedom!
Looks like the jailers are flipping their tops again.
Prisoners have disappeared.
They've been pulled down into hell.
Those silly little fools couldn't be more wrong.
We're here and we're queer!
Woo!
I wouldn't exactly call this hell, would you?
Well, who knows?
Maybe it is.
But if so, at least it's a gay one.
The secret underground where dreams come true.
Woo!
I bid you welcome.
To Impel Down level 5.5, bitches!
A secret garden for all y'all prisoners!
Ah!
This is New Kamaland!
Hee-haw!
They're all queer like me.
Eva!
Watch it, Eva!
What?
Eva!
That's Eva?
The...
The legendary miracle worker?
The queen of Kamabaka kingdom?
Hee-haw!
Emporio Ivankov?
Rescued by Inazuma, Bon Clay is relieved to hear that Eva will cure Luffy's poison.
However, when he discovers the toll that it will take on his friend's body, his joy quickly turns to dread.
Now the battle for Luffy's life truly begins.
On the next Wood Piece, Luffy's treatment begins!
Eva's miraculous power!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Geez!
come on!
we're stronger!
Hungry Arties!